Markham Starr collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1. 2013 accrual: End of the Line and Finest Kind files, March 1, 2010 through March 30, 2010, June 28 2010 through July 30 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 822 TIFF, 2 jpg, 2 pdf, 2 xls, and 1 docx
  - Subseries 2. Finest Kind: The Lobstermen of Corea Maine files, June 28 2010 through July 30 2010, 488 TIFF, 1 pdf, 1 xls
    - Douglas Hooper gets ready to launch a trap on the Haily Devine, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Haily Devine working on the bay in fog, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Haily Devine working on the bay in fog. Owned and worked by Douglas and Wendy Hooper, Wendy is banding a lobster on the back deck. Their son and his girlfriend are working the boat in the background.
    - Douglas and Wendy Hooper working on the Hailey Devine. Wendy Hooper left, Douglas Hooper right, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Douglas and Wendy Hooper working on the Hailey Devine, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Douglas and Wendy Hooper working on the Hailey Devine. Douglas is hauling the next pair of traps while Wendy bands lobsters and fills bait bags. Wendy Hooper left, Douglas Hooper right.
    - Halibut tags for the state of Maine on the dashboard of the Capt. Brennon, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Halibut tags for the state of Maine on the dashboard of the Capt. Brennon. Ethan Whitaker hopes to earn extra money by catching halibut in his spare time. Every halibut taken must be tagged to be legal.
    - View looking towards the mouth of Corea Harbor, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - View looking up towards the head of Corea Harbor, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      View looking up towards the head of Corea Harbor. Crowley's Island forms the other side - it is connected to the mainland by a causeway.
    - View looking towards the mouth of Corea Harbor with the coop on the left, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - View of Corea Harbor with Crowley's Island on the right, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - View looking towards the mouth of Corea Harbor, July 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - View of Corea Harbor, July 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      View of Corea Harbor. Stonework and pilings in foreground were once a lobster pound.
    - View out the mouth of Corea Harbor on a foggy day, June 28, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - View of Corea Harbor, July 01, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Harold "Babe" Crowley - oldest fisherman still fishing at the time of the photos, July 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Harold "Babe" Crowley - oldest fisherman still fishing at the time of the photos. Harold "Babe" Crowley, 80 years old.
    - An automatic pot hauler, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      An automatic pot hauler. Hydraulically operated, two spinning disks form a "V" into which the pot warp is placed to haul the traps. This revolutionized the industry, and allowed fishermen to haul the newer wire traps which have no natural buoyance like the wooden traps did. It also allowed the fishermen to work in deep waters and haul multiple traps at once, saving their backs much effort.
    - A lobster boat at work, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - A boat at work in the bay, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - A boat at work in the bay, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Bait - herring, July 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Bait - herring. Herring is the preferred bait in Corea, but they also use pogies, redfish, and alewives when herring is too expensive or not available.
    - Totes of herring ready to be used as bait, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lone herring on deck, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - View of Corea Harbor - all boats are out fishing, leaving their skiffs on the mooring until they return, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - A boat from Corea nearly disappears in the swell as they work their traps along the coastline, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Boats on their moorings in Corea Harbor, July 28, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jean Symonds, July 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Jean Symonds - at the time this photo was taken she was the second oldest person fishing from Corea.
    - Jean Symonds, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Jean Symonds - one of two female captains in the harbor at time of photos. Has her PHD in nursing and also taught nursing and women's studies at the college level. Lobstered while teaching and after retirement from the college. Fishing 600 traps.
    - Jean Symonds and Jynes Albee hauling traps on boat Finest Kind II. Jean Symonds left, Jynes Albee right, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jean Symonds and Jynes Albee hauling traps on boat Finest Kind II. Jean Symonds left, Jynes Albee right, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jean Symonds and Jynes Albee on Finest Kind II. Jean Symonds left, Jynes Albee right, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jean Symonds and Jynes Albee paddle back from the Finest Kind at the end of the day's work. Jean Symonds front and Jynes Albee back, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Old store on right, July 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Old store on right. This building was used as a grocery store by Jean Symonds and her partner when they first moved to the area. It sat on a wharf, and was later moved ashore for use as a workshop when Jean got into lobstering.
    - Jean Symonds putting on her foul weather gear, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jean Symonds removing a lobster from a trap, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jean Symonds at the helm of Finest Kind II, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jean Symonds, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jean Symonds and Jynes Albee working their gear. Jynes Albee left, Jean Symonds right, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Boats on their moorings in Corea Harbor, July 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - The crew of the Jewels at work in the bay, July 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Boats waiting in the mouth of the harbor for a space to open on the docks at the coop, July 23, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - The Jackie's Way at work in the bay, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      The Jackie's Way at work in the bay. Owned by Leigh Farnsworth, one of two women captains in Corea at that time.
    - Jordyn Knowles - sterning for her boyfriend on Fishin' w/ Jordyn, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Jordyn Knowles - sterning for her boyfriend on Fishin' w/ Jordyn. There are many women sterning on boats in Corea.
    - Jordyn Knowles - sterning for her boyfriend on Fishin' w/ Jordyn, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jynes Albee on the Finest Kind II, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Jynes Albee on the Finest Kind II. She is an apprentice under Jean Symonds. Before fishermen can get their full lobstering license and captain their own boat they must undergo an apprenticeship period.
    - Jynes Albee sterns on the Finest Kind II, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jynes Albee sterns on the Finest Kind II, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jynes Albee sterns on the Finest Kind II, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jynes Albee sterns on the Finest Kind II, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jynes Albee measures a lobster, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Jynes Albee and Jean Symonds tending traps. Jynes Albee left, Jean Symonds right, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - The Karen Jo approaches the dock at the coop to unload her day's catch, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Kevin Scully writes a receipt for a lobsterman, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Kevin Scully writes a receipt for a lobsterman, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Kevin Scully, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Killing Time steams amongst buoys, July 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Hauling traps on Killing Time. Crystal Gewlas left, Walter Moore Jr. right, July 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Hauling traps on Killing Time, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Hauling traps on Killing Time, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Hauling traps on Killing Time. Crystal Gewlas left, Walter Moore Jr. right, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Crystal Gewlas loads bait onto the Killing Time at the coop, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Hauling traps on Killing Time, July 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Killing Time steams to next pair of traps to be hauled, July 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Hauling traps on Killing Time, July 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - The Kimberley J heads for the coop at the end of the day's work. Another husband and wife team operating from the bay, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay. Richard Melhorn left, Charles Haycock right, July 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay. Richard Melhorn filling a bait bag, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay. Richard Melhorn left, Charles Haycock right, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay. Richard Melhorn right, Charles Haycock left, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay. Richard Melhorn left, Charles Haycock right, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay. Richard Melhorn left, Charles Haycock right, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay. Richard Melhorn left, Charles Haycock right, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance heads to sea, July 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay. Richard Melhorn right, Charles Haycock left, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay. Richard Melhorn left, Charles Haycock right, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lass Chance fishing in Gouldsboro Bay, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Laurie Jane heads out of the harbor, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Laurie Jane heads out of the harbor. Owned by Mark Young.
    - Laurie Jane heads out of the harbor, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Laurie Jane heads to the next set of traps to be hauled, July 23, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Laurie Jane heads to the next set of traps to be hauled. Owned by Mark Young.
    - Shackle and tongs used to raise and lower bait totes at the coop, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Bruce Hartford banding lobsters between trap haulings, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Bruce Hartford pulling down one of the next pair of traps to be launched in a new location, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lisa Lynn - Dan Whitaker's boat, loaded with traps to be set offshore that day, July 20, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Crystal Gewlas loading bait onto Killing Time, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Wharf on right and railway for hauling lobster cars on left, July 20, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Wharf on right and railway for hauling lobster cars on left. While there are no railways that can haul boats in the harbor (all boats are hauled with a hydraulic trailer from a launch ramp) there are the remains of several small railways used to haul lobster cars - the floating boxes lobstermen use to store live lobsters in. Free flow of water through the crates keep the lobsters alive until sold. Cars also double as docks in the harbor.
    - Wharf on right and railway for hauling lobster cars on left, July 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Wharf on right and railway for hauling lobster cars on left, July 25, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lobsters wait to be measured and banded, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - One lobster escapes over the top and into the bait tub, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Removing lobsters from a trap just hauled, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - The catch, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Banded Lobsters, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Banded Lobsters in a basket, July 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lobsters in a tote, July 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lobsters in a tote, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lobsters wait to be measured and banded, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Lobsters on the scales at the coop, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Lobsters on the scales at the coop. Lobsters are sorted by hard or soft shell and placed 90 pounds per tote.
    - Bruce Hartford watches the sun rise while waiting to launch a new pair of traps on the Lisa Marie, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - The Capt. Brennon runs home in rough weather, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Upper Corea Harbor at dead low tide, July 20, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Upper Corea Harbor at dead low tide. Fishermen's shacks, wharves, and gear still ring the harbor - very unusual even for Maine by this time. There was only one non-fishing boat in the harbor at the time these photos were taken.
    - Lass Chance fishing in the bay in a fog bank, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - A sternman places lobsters into a tote at the coop, July 23, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Upper Corea Harbor at high tide, July 20, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Upper Corea Harbor at high tide. Fishermen's shacks, wharves, and gear still ring the harbor - very unusual even for Maine by this time. There was only one non-fishing boat in the harbor at the time these photos were taken.
    - Boats and gear in Corea Harbor, July 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Tim McLain empties a trap aboard the Nana Marie, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Mike Bragdon weighs the catch just landed at the coop, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Mike Bragdon lowers bait to a waiting fisherman at the coop, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Mike Bragdon removes a tote of lobsters from a boat, July 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Mike Bragdon removes a tote of lobsters from a boat. Mike Bragdon
    - Mike Bragdon shoveling bate into an exactor inside the coop bait room, July 20, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Hauling a trap on the Miss Chriss in the bay, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Hauling a trap on the Miss Chriss in the bay, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - At work on the Miss Chriss in the bay, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Harold Crowley watches the Lisa Lynn ahead of him during the morning commute, July 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - View of Corea Harbor waterfront, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Early photo of Corea Harbor, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Early photo of Corea Harbor. Photograph is from an family album owned by Mrs. Morna Briggs. Her husband was a lobsterman as is one of her sons. She also lobstered with her husband as he got older. Photo of a photo.
    - Early photo of Corea Harbor, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Early photo of Corea Harbor, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Early photo of Corea Harbor, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Early photo of Corea Harbor, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Old house on the way to Corea, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Old house on the way to Corea. At the time of these photos, the US economy was in the tank and there were many abandoned homes in the area surrounding Corea. Some were empty and for sale, many seemed to be abandoned.
    - Early wooden lobster boat at launching, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Early wooden lobster boat at launching. Photograph is from an family album owned by Mrs. Morna Briggs. Her husband was a lobsterman as is one of her sons. She also lobstered with her husband as he got older. I believe this was one of her husbands boats. Photo of a photo.
    - Man rowing out to his boat in a skiff, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Man rowing out to his boat in a skiff. Photograph is from an family album owned by Mrs. Morna Briggs. Her husband was a lobsterman as is one of her sons. She also lobstered with her husband as he got older. Photo of a photo.
    - Very old fisherman's shack, July 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Very old fisherman's shack. Barely standing on the few piles left of the wharf, this shack has lost its roof and won't last much longer. It is visible in some of the very early photos of the harbor.
    - The Cynthia Jean heads for her traps, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - The Padasa at work along the rocky coastline, July 29, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - The Padasa tied to a wharf for low tide, July 23, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      The Padasa tied to a wharf for low tide. Fishermen often tie their boats to wharves when they want to inspect the bottoms of their boats or effect minor repairs.
    - The Pamela Ann leaves Corea for the day's work, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      The Pamela Ann leaves Corea for the day's work. Owned by Harold "Babe" Crowley.
    - The Pamela Ann in Corea harbor, July 20, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      The Pamela Ann in Corea harbor. Owned by Harold "Babe" Crowley.
    - Boats in the harbor at the end of the day, June 28, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Boats in the harbor at the end of the day.
    - Working on the Pamela Ann. Brandon empties the trap. Babe Crowley, left, Brandon Sprague right, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - A tote of pogies to be used as bait, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      A tote of pogies to be used as bait. At the time of the photos, herring was hard to get and pogies were brought in to help. Corean fishermen did not like to use them.
    - A tote of pogies to be used as bait, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Pot-of-Gold sits on the beach so the owner can inspect the bottom during low tide, July 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Boats waiting in the mouth of the harbor for a space to open on the docks at the coop, July 23, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Boats waiting in the mouth of the harbor for a space to open on the docks at the coop. The little boat Pot-of-Gold was towed in by the Fundy Wanderer after developing engine problems. Fishermen from the harbor always helped others that needed it, knowing their turn could soon come. One fisherman remarked they only called the Coast Guard as a last resort.
    - Pot-of-Gold works in the fog as the Courtney-Leanne comes home, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Pot-of-Gold works in the fog as another boat heads out to sea, July 21, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Miles of line are needed to fish the 800 traps allowed each fisherman, June 28, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - A vessel (I believe it is Pretty Penny) heads out of the stony entrance to Corea's harbor, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Pretty Penny heading to her traps offshore, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Daily posting on 6/2/10 of the price paid that day for lobsters landed, June 30, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Daily posting on 6/2/10 of the price paid that day for lobsters landed. Prices are for old shell (hard) New Shell (soft) and selects per pound.
    - Narda Jean at work offshore, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Narda Jean at work offshore. She is from Prospect Harbor - the next harbor over.
    - The captain of the Virgo makes a long reach to the buoys with a boathook, July 22, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Boats in the harbor at anchor, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Rebecca B comes back to Corea Harbor, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Rebecca B comes back to Corea Harbor. Note the lighthouse in the distance - Petit Manan light.
    - Rebecca B running to her next traps, July 28, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Typical skiff on a mooring in the harbor, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Reflections of a boat in the harbor, July 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Reflections of a boat in the harbor, July 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Reflections of a boat and a skiff in the harbor, July 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Rock crabs are often caught in the traps, and if enough of them can be collected they too are brought back to the coop for sale, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Gear in the harbor, July 02, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Gear in the harbor, July 20, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Gear in the harbor, July 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Gear in the harbor, July 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Rough N' Ready returns to Corea, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Reflections of a boat in the harbor, July 24, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Hooked rug - a map of Corea done in 1955 by Ruth Storm, July 25, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - A sea robin that was caught in the trap, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      A sea robin that was caught in the trap. Often fishermen leave them in the trap as additional bait.
    - Early photograph of fishermen in Corea Harbor purse seining bait, July 27, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Early photograph of fishermen in Corea Harbor purse seining bait. When schools of herring come into the small harbors, fishermen took advantage and netted them for bait from these small boats. They would also "torch" them at night - use a torch light to attract the fish and then scoop them up with dip nets. Photograph is from an family album owned by Mrs. Morna Briggs. Her husband was a lobsterman as is one of her sons. She also lobstered with her husband as he got older. Photo of a photo.
    - Fisherman's Shack and wharf in Corea Harbor, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
      Fisherman's Shack and wharf in Corea Harbor. These workshops were more important back in the days when fishermen made all of their own gear.
    - Fisherman's Shack and wharf in Corea Harbor, July 02, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Fisherman's Shack and wharf in Corea Harbor, July 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Fisherman's Shack and wharf in Corea Harbor, July 18, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Fisherman's Shack and wharf in Corea Harbor, July 19, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Fisherman's Shack and wharf in Corea Harbor, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Fisherman's Shack and wharf in Corea Harbor, July 26, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Fisherman's Shack and wharf in Corea Harbor, July 20, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Fisherman's Shack and wharf in Corea Harbor, July 25, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Fisherman's Shack and wharf in Corea Harbor, July 25, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF
    - Fisherman's Shack and wharf in Corea Harbor, July 20, 2010, afc2013031_dc001; 1 TIFF